<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mahe Iram Khan</title>
    <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mahe Iram Khan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Guillotine, Flowers, and Mandala</title>
      <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/life-blogs/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/life-blogs/week-1/</guid>
      <description>It’s been one week since we stepped into 2024. I would like to briefly summarize what the first week of 2024 was like for me.
I started the year with lots of flowers around me! I love giving myself and receiving from others a colorful and fragrant bouquet of flowers. Below are some of the flowers from this week:
I memorized the lyrics of my university’s anthem! It’s written in Urdu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bearable Pain in The Foot</title>
      <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/life-blogs/the-bearable-pain-in-the-foot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/life-blogs/the-bearable-pain-in-the-foot/</guid>
      <description>We had only been friends for a few weeks when A.H. proposed we take a stroll in the Tiergarten.
It was a bright but very cold morning, there was a promise of snow. The garden was mostly yellow and dry this time of the year. But it was still a desirable change from Central Berlin streets which were very pretty, but weren&amp;rsquo;t especially green.
We agreed the garden would be lush during the summer months and promised to visit again in summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Accidental Emending</title>
      <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/life-blogs/an-accidental-emending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/life-blogs/an-accidental-emending/</guid>
      <description>Since coming back from my week long stay at grandmother’s village, my total mess of a sleep schedule has miraculously fixed itself. Perhaps this self emending is not too miraculous after all.
In the village I would sleep on a charpayi on the roof with my grandmother, aunt, uncle and his children. Of course electricity is still erratic in that North Indian village, people call it bed time when the sky turns dark and wakey-wakey when the dawn breaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Struggles</title>
      <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/everybody-struggles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/everybody-struggles/</guid>
      <description>I have been delaying writing this Outreachy blog for over two weeks now. Aagghh! I kept thinking I’ll write it up when I have the perfect struggle story to share, when I am in the perfect mood to write. But that doesn’t happen. Waiting for ‘the inspiration’ to write is the best way to make sure that you never write at all.
Better done than perfect!
The theme for this blog (as suggested by the Outreachy folks) is ‘an open source vocabulary term’ that I once didn’t know and eventually learnt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing Packages To conda-forge Using Grayskull</title>
      <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/contributing-packages-to-conda-forge-using-grayskull/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/contributing-packages-to-conda-forge-using-grayskull/</guid>
      <description>When contributing packages to conda-forge, Grayskull can make your life much easier. Grayskull generates recipes for Python packages hosted on PyPI. As the introduction for Grayskull reads; “The main goal of this project is to generate concise recipes for conda-forge.”
In this tutorial we learn how to contribute a Python package to the conda-forge channel using Grayskull to generate the recipe.
Let us get started.
Install grayskull using conda through the conda-forge channel: conda install -c conda-forge grayskull Fork and clone the conda-forge staged-recipes repository from GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Core Values and Outreachy</title>
      <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/my-core-values-and-outreachy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/my-core-values-and-outreachy/</guid>
      <description>In my previous blog I wrote about the Outreachy application process and my experience during the contribution period.
A lot has happened since then. For one; I got selected. (Yippie!)
And second; the internship has already begun. Week one completed today.
Outreachy encourages its interns to write a blog every two weeks. I plan on to write one every week. This week’s blog is going to be about me, my core values and my motivation behind applying at Outreachy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Outreachy Application</title>
      <link>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/my-outreachy-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://forgottenprogramme.github.io/work-blogs/my-outreachy-application/</guid>
      <description>Last year my initial application at Outreachy was rejected because I had submitted it on the last day.
I had invested quite some time in my initial application and felt a bit dejected that the folks at Outreachy hadn’t even reviewed my application.
That year, reported Outreachy, there was an “overwhelmingly large” number of applications and Outreachy decided not to review those submitted on the day of the deadline.
This year, I decided I was going to be vigilant and proactive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
